<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-11-26T23:08:20+03:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">ShowStopperTheSecond</title><subtitle>Javid Norouzi</subtitle><author><name>Javid Norouzi</name></author><entry><title type="html">Follow Your Dreams</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/posts/2022/03/FollowYourDreams/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Follow Your Dreams" /><published>2022-03-14T00:00:00+03:30</published><updated>2022-03-14T00:00:00+03:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/posts/2022/03/FollowYourDreams</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/posts/2022/03/FollowYourDreams/"><![CDATA[<p>The Openning:</p>

<p>First, we are told from childhood that everything we want to do is impossible. As we grow older, layers of prejudice, fear, and guilt accumulate, burying our personal calling deep within our soul. But it is still there. To disinter our dream, we need courage.</p>

<p>Second, we fear hurting those we love by abandoning everything to pursue our dream. But love is a stimulus, not a hindrance. Those who genuinely wish us well want us to be happy and will accompany us on our journey.</p>

<p>Third, we fear the defeats we will encounter on the path to our dream. We suffer more when it doesn’t work out because we cannot fall back on the old excuse that we didn’t really want it anyway. We must have patience and know that the Universe is conspiring in our favor.</p>

<p>Fourth, we fear realizing our dream. The mere possibility of getting what we want fills us with guilt. We forget about the obstacles we overcame, the suffering we endured, and the things we had to give up to get this far. We must believe ourselves worthy of the thing we fought so hard to get.</p>

<p>Living our personal calling is important because once we overcome the obstacles and fulfill our dream, we are filled with a greater sense of euphoria and confidence. We start to live with enthusiasm and pleasure. Unexpected suffering passes more quickly than suffering that is apparently bearable.</p>

<p>In the end, we become an instrument of God, helping the Soul of the World, and understanding why we are here. The secret of life is to fall seven times and get up eight times. Each day and each hour is part of the good fight.</p>

<!-- Headings are cool
======

You can have many headings
======

Aren't headings cool?
------ -->]]></content><author><name>Javid Norouzi</name></author><category term="Books" /><category term="PauloCoelho" /><category term="TheAlchemist" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Openning:]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Deep Hatred</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/posts/2022/03/Deepest-hatered/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Deep Hatred" /><published>2022-03-06T00:00:00+03:30</published><updated>2022-03-06T00:00:00+03:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/posts/2022/03/Deepest-hatered</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/posts/2022/03/Deepest-hatered/"><![CDATA[<p>“I cannot forgive your eyes that saw Faputa and her siblings as nothing more than appetizing. Your mouths that use the same words and  prayers as  mother, Those mouths I cannot forgive. I cannot forgive your shapes that continue to blaspheme mother with your being. Your lives that continue to exist, I cannot forgive.</p>

<p>Your intentions, I cannot forgive. Nor your joy, nor your grief, nor your deeds. I absolutely will not allow them to continue. Until you’re all reduced to ashes, I cannot permiss your existence. Everything I was born not to forget, for this day, for this moment. How I tired of waiting. The time I have waited also cannot be forgiven. I will exterminate all of you.”</p>

<figure class="">
  <img src="/assets/images/faputa.jpg" alt="this is a placeholder image" /><figcaption>
      Faputa

    </figcaption></figure>]]></content><author><name>Javid Norouzi</name></author><category term="Made in Abyss" /><category term="Faputa" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I cannot forgive your eyes that saw Faputa and her siblings as nothing more than appetizing. Your mouths that use the same words and prayers as mother, Those mouths I cannot forgive. I cannot forgive your shapes that continue to blaspheme mother with your being. Your lives that continue to exist, I cannot forgive.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Longest-Running Evolution Experiment</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/posts/2022/01/TheLongestRunningEvolutionExperiment/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Longest-Running Evolution Experiment" /><published>2022-01-27T00:00:00+03:30</published><updated>2022-01-27T00:00:00+03:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/posts/2022/01/The-Longest-Running-Evolution-Experiment</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/posts/2022/01/TheLongestRunningEvolutionExperiment/"><![CDATA[<!-- Courtesy of embedresponsively.com -->

<div class="responsive-video-container">
    <iframe src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/0Kx4Y9TVMGg" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen="" allowfullscreen=""></iframe>
  </div>

<!-- This post will show up by default. To disable scheduling of future posts, edit `config.yml` and set `future: false`.  -->]]></content><author><name>Javid Norouzi</name></author><category term="Simulation" /><category term="Genetic Algorithm" /><category term="Artificial Life" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Green Knight</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/posts/2021/12/Green-Knight/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Green Knight" /><published>2021-12-15T00:00:00+03:30</published><updated>2021-12-15T00:00:00+03:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/posts/2021/12/GreenKnight</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/posts/2021/12/Green-Knight/"><![CDATA[<p>“Green is the color of earth of living things, of life. We deck our halls with it and dye our linens. But should it come creeping up the cobbles, we scrub it out, fast as we can. When it blooms beneath our skin, we bleed it out, And when we together all, find that our reach has exceeded our grasp, we cut it down. We stamp it out we spread ourselves atop it and smother it beneath our bellies, but it comes back, it does not dally, nor does it wait to plot conspire. Pull it out by the roots one day and then next, there it is, creeping in around the edges. whilst we’re off looking for red it comes green. Red is the color of lust, but green is what lust leaves behind, in heart, in womb, Green is what is left when odore fades, when passion dies, when we die, too. When you go, your footprints will fill with grass. Moss shall cover your tombstone, and as the sun rises, green shall spread over all, in all it’s shades and hues. It’s verdigris will overtake your swords and your coins and your battlements and, try as you might, all you hold dear will succumb to it. your skin, your bones, your virtue.”</p>

<!-- Headings are cool
======

You can have many headings
======

Aren't headings cool?
------ -->]]></content><author><name>Javid Norouzi</name></author><category term="Movie" /><category term="GreenKnight" /><category term="Quotes" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Green is the color of earth of living things, of life. We deck our halls with it and dye our linens. But should it come creeping up the cobbles, we scrub it out, fast as we can. When it blooms beneath our skin, we bleed it out, And when we together all, find that our reach has exceeded our grasp, we cut it down. We stamp it out we spread ourselves atop it and smother it beneath our bellies, but it comes back, it does not dally, nor does it wait to plot conspire. Pull it out by the roots one day and then next, there it is, creeping in around the edges. whilst we’re off looking for red it comes green. Red is the color of lust, but green is what lust leaves behind, in heart, in womb, Green is what is left when odore fades, when passion dies, when we die, too. When you go, your footprints will fill with grass. Moss shall cover your tombstone, and as the sun rises, green shall spread over all, in all it’s shades and hues. It’s verdigris will overtake your swords and your coins and your battlements and, try as you might, all you hold dear will succumb to it. your skin, your bones, your virtue.”]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hedonistic Utopia</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/posts/2021/01/Hedonistic-Utopia/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hedonistic Utopia" /><published>2021-01-03T00:00:00+03:30</published><updated>2021-01-03T00:00:00+03:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/posts/2021/01/Hedonistic-Utopia</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/posts/2021/01/Hedonistic-Utopia/"><![CDATA[<p>“Hedonistic Utopias that the old reformers imagined. A world of fear and treachery is torment, a world of trampling and being trampled upon, a world which will grow not less but more merciless as it refines itself. Progress in our world will be progress towards more pain. The old civilizations claimed that they were founded on love or justice. Ours is founded upon hatred. In our world there will be no emotions except fear, rage, triumph, and self- abasement. Everything else we shall destroy everything. Already we are breaking down the habits of thought which have survived from before the Revolution. We have cut the links between child and parent, and between man and man, and between man and woman. No one dares trust a wife or a child or a friend any longer. But in the future there will be no wives and no friends. Children will be taken from their mothers at birth, as one takes eggs from a hen. The sex instinct will be eradicated. Procreation will be an annual formality like the renewal of a ration card. We shall abolish the orgasm. Our neurologists are at work upon it now. There will be no loyalty, except loyalty towards the Party. There will be no love, except the love of Big Brother. There will be no laughter, except the laugh of triumph over a defeated enemy. There will be no art, no literature, no science. When we are omnipotent we shall have no more need of science. There will be no distinction between beauty and ugliness. There will be no curiosity, no enjoyment of the process of life. All competing pleasures will be destroyed. But always – do not forget this, Winston – always there will be the intoxication of power, constantly increasing and constantly growing subtler. Always, at every moment, there will be the thrill of victory, the sensation of trampling on an enemy who is helpless. If you want a picture of the future, imagine a boot stamping on a human face – for ever.’”</p>

<!-- Headings are cool
======

You can have many headings
======

Aren't headings cool?
------ -->]]></content><author><name>Javid Norouzi</name></author><category term="George Orwell" /><category term="1984" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Hedonistic Utopias that the old reformers imagined. A world of fear and treachery is torment, a world of trampling and being trampled upon, a world which will grow not less but more merciless as it refines itself. Progress in our world will be progress towards more pain. The old civilizations claimed that they were founded on love or justice. Ours is founded upon hatred. In our world there will be no emotions except fear, rage, triumph, and self- abasement. Everything else we shall destroy everything. Already we are breaking down the habits of thought which have survived from before the Revolution. We have cut the links between child and parent, and between man and man, and between man and woman. No one dares trust a wife or a child or a friend any longer. But in the future there will be no wives and no friends. Children will be taken from their mothers at birth, as one takes eggs from a hen. The sex instinct will be eradicated. Procreation will be an annual formality like the renewal of a ration card. We shall abolish the orgasm. Our neurologists are at work upon it now. There will be no loyalty, except loyalty towards the Party. There will be no love, except the love of Big Brother. There will be no laughter, except the laugh of triumph over a defeated enemy. There will be no art, no literature, no science. When we are omnipotent we shall have no more need of science. There will be no distinction between beauty and ugliness. There will be no curiosity, no enjoyment of the process of life. All competing pleasures will be destroyed. But always – do not forget this, Winston – always there will be the intoxication of power, constantly increasing and constantly growing subtler. Always, at every moment, there will be the thrill of victory, the sensation of trampling on an enemy who is helpless. If you want a picture of the future, imagine a boot stamping on a human face – for ever.’”]]></summary></entry></feed>